freevectormaps.com 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy | Free Vector Maps

## Your privacy is critically important to Free Vector Maps.

At Free Vector Maps we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * In our product, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law or protect our rights.

It is Free Vector Maps’ policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. 

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Free Vector Maps collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Free Vector Maps’ purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Free Vector Maps’ visitors use its website. From time to time, Free Vector Maps may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. Free Vector Maps also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Free Vector Maps does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information Certain visitors to Free Vector Maps’ websites choose to interact with Free Vector Maps in ways that require Free Vector Maps to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Free Vector Maps gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we may ask visitors who sign up for an username and an optional email address. Free Vector Maps collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Free Vector Maps. Free Vector Maps does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

Free Vector Maps may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Free Vector Maps may monitor the most popular maps and may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Free Vector Maps does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information Free Vector Maps discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Free Vector Maps’ behalf or to provide services available at Free Vector Maps’ websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Free Vector Maps’ websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Free Vector Maps will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Free Vector Maps discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Free Vector Maps believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Free Vector Maps, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Free Vector Maps website and have supplied your email address, Free Vector Maps may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Free Vector Maps and our products, and we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send Free Vector Maps a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help Free Vector Maps clarify or respond to your request or to help Free Vector Maps support other users. Free Vector Maps takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Free Vector Maps uses cookies to help Free Vector Maps identify and track visitors, their usage of Free Vector Maps website, and their website access preferences. Free Vector Maps visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Free Vector Maps’ websites, with the drawback that certain features of Free Vector Maps’ websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Free Vector Maps may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Free Vector Maps’ sole discretion. Free Vector Maps encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

This privacy policy was graciously appropriated from Automattic who were generous enough to have made it available under a [Creative Commons Share Alike](http://go2.wordpress.com/?id=725X1342&site=automattic.wordpress.com&url=http%3A%2F%2Fcreativecommons.org%2Flicenses%2Fby-sa%2F2.5%2F&sref=http%3A%2F%2Fautomattic.com%2Fprivacy%2F) license. Visit them at [Wordpress.com](http://www.wordpress.com/).
